[The late Kim Joowon]
We are not done shooting yet.
Hang in there a little longer.
Mom.
I quit being an actor.
I'm going to be a director.
You are nothing if you're not an actor!
Maybe you're right,
I'm nothing if I'm not an actor.
But...
even so,
I can't give up on what I want to do.
I'm sorry.
Luka, I just remembered who you are.
But why
are you dying in my arms?
If the end of love is death,
it's too unfair.
A tragic ending where you save
your loved one but die yourself...
[The Little Mermaid]
is way too unfair.
I want to see a brand new ending.
A happy ending
for the mermaid and her lover.
Then,
how about calling this story
"The Mermaid Prince"?
Jung Yihyun?
Are you okay?
-I really missed you.
-Huh?
[Hongseok]
[Park Seonghyun]
[Shin Yongseok] [Shin Junseop] [Ha Yosep]
[Play Me]
How could a dream feel so real?
Are you sober now?
Gosh, my back is killing me.
So you brought me home?
Hurry up,
get ready and come to the theater.
-Why?
-Huh?
Today is the audition day.
We have to cast the lead role.
You're eliminated.
Thank you for coming.
There's no one else. No one!
That was the last applicant.
Hey, what exactly are you looking for?
Someone with clear eyes,
and slightly thick lips...
Someone with a naturally refreshing vibe.
Hey, who else in the world
fits that description but me?
What's wrong?
Look at me.
Look at how refreshing I am.
Shall we start?
It's me, Eden.
The person
who saved you in the storm
that day was me.
He's a celebrity, isn't he?
I just hung out with him a few times.
Since then, I haven't forgotten you
for a single moment.
I was afraid you'd be disappointed
if you saw me.
But now I have to tell you...
that I... am that mermaid.
Hey, he's the one.
He's exactly who you are looking for...
You're eliminated.
Why?
Well. Please take your leave.
Wait.
Why did you... eliminate me?
I don't understand.
Because I didn't like your acting.
Hey, what are you doing?
Honestly, you liked it.
Your gaze looked completely different.
Does that answer your question?
I want to know why you didn't like it.
Your emotion was wrong.
When Luka confessed
his true identity to Eden,
what he felt wasn't certainty,
but anxiety.
This is a confession scene.
How can a confession lack certainty?
Eden has never given
enough sense of security.
How could Luka have certainty?
Love is not decided
by the other person's reaction.
As long as my heart is full of sincerity,
that's enough.
If it's true love,
you must muster up courage...
Courage?
What if the other person betrays them?
Well!
Shall we end this here?
Director.
Do you have any reason
why you must act in this play?
What you just said...
"One day,
we must stand on stage together."
I'm unable to understand it...
and it makes me very frustrated.
It also made me feel kind of arrogant,
Director—
no—
Mr. Jung Yihyun.
Because...
I want to protect you.
How did he know?
That aside,
you two know each other, right?
I can tell from the vibe.
What's wrong?
I'm your manager, I need to know.
He's just a friend
I knew from my school days.
Isn't that better? Old acquaintances.
It's easier to build chemistry.
Not him.
Hey, you saw it too—
his acting.
He is the Luka we've been looking for.
Are you mixing personal feelings in this?
You're eliminated.
How could he eliminate someone
so directly like that?
Because I don't like your acting.
What if the other person betrays them?
But seriously, why is he
acting like this to me?
What did I do wrong?
He's the one who suddenly lost contact,
why is he taking it out on me...
I miss you so much.
Huh?
If so, why did you say you miss me
and kiss me?
You've passed.
[You've passed.]
Oh!
[But on one condition: you have to spend
a night with Jung Yihyun.]
But on one condition:
you have to spend
a night with Jung Yihyun.
[The Mermaid Prince]
[To K, this script is written for you.]
That's mine.
What's wrong?
Wait a minute.
Oh, wait a minute.
So Luka noticed something at this point,
which is why he said that.
Ah, so that's why
the emotion is like this.
How about Luka jumping into the sea...
sir?
Well, I think when emotions
reach a peak,
one might actually do that...
sir.
Let's change it to that, then.
This reminds me of the past.
Didn't we also analyze scripts
back in high school?
Then let's change it to
Eden looking for Luka.
Was it "Hamlet" back then?
Ah, it was "King Lear."
The next scene.
Ah, it was "Romeo and Juliet."
And we were discussing
who would play Romeo.
"A Midsummer Night's Dream."
It was that.
Really?
Since you remembered,
why didn't you say so earlier?
Because those things aren't important.
Let's just focus on
reading this script for now.
Director.
Can I be nosy and ask you one more thing?
Go ahead.
The condition was that I spend a night
with you, right?
How are we going
to spend this night, Director?
Director?
A night?
Yihyun said something like that?
You're heading home, right?
Shall we...
I was going to check the warehouse first.
What about dinner?
I can skip it.
See you tomorrow.
Wait!
Let's go.
What?
Today is perfect.
Sir, 2 candied haws, please.
Don't tell me
this is your first time
eating candied haws?
I am very strict about my figure.
I used to be an actor too.
Hey, isn't that Jung Yihyun?
Yes, it really is him.
We need to take pictures.
Hurry up and take pictures!
If you're done eating, shall we
do something to maintain your figure?
Run!
As a director,
I should be choosing Kang Jae-on.
Professionalism.
Professionalism...
Then...
I'll just make him reject it.
Although I really want to work with him,
I can't help it if he doesn't want to.
[Kang Jae-on]
[You've passed.]
You've passed.
But on one condition:
you have to spend
a night with Jung Yihyun.
[But on one condition: you have to spend
a night with Jung Yihyun.]
[Okay!
See you at the theater tomorrow! ^^]
Okay, see you at the theater tomorrow!
Why are we meeting at the theater?